Guide to the George Baehr Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- PERSONAL PAPERS, 1915-1978; Series III; 2 linear feet (5 boxes)
  - General material
    - Correspondence and related material re: oral history, Columbia University, 1975-1976, undated (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Transcript draft, oral history interview conducted by Louis Sheaffer, Columbia University, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Transcript, oral history interview conducted by Louis Sheaffer, Columbia University, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence re: condolences, tributes and obituaries, 1978 October-November (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Photographs
    - Album, "Expedition to the Balkans and Russia/American Red Cross Typhus Commission,", 1915-1916 (Box 10, Folder 18-20)
    - Album, "Expedition to the Balkans and Russia/Red Cross Typhus Commission," loose material, 1915-1916 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Album, "World War I ,", 1917-1919 (Box 10, Folder 22-24)
    - Album, "World War I," loose material, 1917-1919 (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Undated prints, Circa 1942-1972 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Dated prints, 1948-1977 (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Album, personal photographs, 1957-1964, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Album, personal photographs (photographs 1-23), 1959-1968 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Album, personal photographs, (photographs 24-46), 1959-1968 (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Album, personal photographs, (photographs 47-65), 1959-1968 (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Album, "Dedication of the Hilleboe Auditorium in the Research Studies Center of the Roswell Park Memorial Institute,", 1974 July 26 (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Photographs, undated
      See: box 13, folder 5
  - Scrapbooks
    - Presentation volume, George Baehr testimonial dinner, 1957 June 5 (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - Commemorative volume, George Baehr testimonial dinner, 1957 June 5 (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - Scrapbooks 1-5, 1912-1963
      See: box 13, folders 1-4
- OVERSIZE
  - Scrapbook no. 1, 1912-1913, 1933-1941 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbook no. 2, 1941-1947 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Scrapbook no. 3, 1942, 1947-1949 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Scrapbook no. 4-5, 1943-1963 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 13, Folder 5)